Thank you.
どうも
Nice to meet you.
初めましてー
初 めましてー
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いねー
Leah is now...
リアさんが今...
You look really young, but
めちゃくちゃ若く見えるんだけど、
How old are you now?
今、いくつくらい?
I'm a teenager now.
今、10代です
Seriously?
マジかー
I thought he was young, but he was actually a teenager.
若い若いって思ったけど、本当に10代だったんだ
yes.
はい
Oh my gosh.
やばー
You came here today too,
今日もここ来てくれたわけだけど、
What do you usually do?
普段何してる?
I usually stream games.
普段は、 ゲームの 配信してます
picture?
え?
Are you playing any game streaming?
ゲームの配信って なんかプレイしてるやつ?
that's right.
そうです
Huh, what kind of game?
え、どんなゲーム?
Hmm, it's been quite popular lately.
うーん、最近 結構流行ってる
What about Epex and Wherecord?
エペックスとか、 あとは ホエアコード?
I love it.
大好きです
Eh, I thought it would be a game about making some kind of reproduction.
えー、もうちょっと なんか 再現作ったりするゲームかと思った
Next up, I'm playing a game that's a little more masculine.
ら 次のとなんかちょっと 男まさりなゲーム やってるんで
I really enjoyed the feeling of hitting my opponent.
相 手打つ感覚とか すごい 楽しんだよ
I agree.
そうですね
Wow, it looks like I'm going to push it,
えー、すごい 押しちゃうかに見えて、
Is it actually a carnivore?
実は肉食系なのかな?
Properly.
ちゃん と
That's cute.
と、可愛いね
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏とかは?
not present.
いない
A lot of hedging.
いっぱいヘッジなこと
I'm a little worried now.
今、ちょっと 悩んだ
Accident.
意外
What can't you see?
何見られんのか
You're wearing really sexy underwear.
すごいセクシーな 下着付けてるね
It's so damn delicious I'm listening to it.
めちゃくちゃういして 聞いてるじゃん
I realized that and went blank.
気づいて真っ白になっちゃった
Stroke me while looking at me.
こっち見ながら 撫でて
Don't use your hands.
手使わないで
Can it dry this far?
ここまで 乾いたりできる?
This too will become dry.
これも 乾いてるようになるの
mosquito?
か?
What should we do together next time?
次、 一緒に何で やってしまうか
Ah, of course it's a little small.
あー、そりゃそりゃ ちょっとちい
There are people who are starting to care.
かまってきてる人が いる
Does it hit this far?
ここまで当たる?
Yeah.
うん
Are you eating your feet?
足 食べてる?
Is it okay if I put my foot out?
足出したらダメ?
Is it bad if my legs are all out?
足いっぱい出したらダメ?
No.
ダメ